cathyscraving.net 2016-11-01

# CATHYS CRAVING.COM

**Privacy Policy**

Our Commitment To Privacy 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

The Information We Collect: 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on this ACG Web Design website. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Email address: 

The Way We Use This Information: Is solely to enable us to send occasional emails to interested persons detailing our latest offers and website news. 

Our Commitment To Data Security 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information: 

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by applying via the email address you submitted to us. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

How To Contact Us: 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email by; **[Clicking HERE](mailto:cathy@cathyscraving.com?subject=Privacy%20Issue)**.
